going
to go.
>> Yep. All good.
>> All right, cool. K, you can start us
off.
>> We can go to Nikki.
>> Hey, Andrew.
um you know, what does it mean to you to
get two more years here and kind of what
are you personally hope to accomplish
over the next two years?
>> Uh yeah, super stoked uh to get such a
good deal done. Um you know, shout out
to everyone involved on my side and here
in the building in the front office. Um
so much love around the building today,
uh being back. Um but expectations are
high, you know, um trying to write the
ship. Um and you know, ultimately just
get back to the big game and try to walk
away with the ring in this next year.
>> You're you're now into what your third
offensive coordinator since being here.
Um kind of what is that transition like
for you and and what what's your
approach to kind of adjusting to
whatever the new system might be with
David?
>> Yeah. Um super stoked for Blau and um
and couldn't be more supportive of Cliff
and and his role too. Um it's just kind
of the nature of the business in in some
some parts of the league, some teams.
Um, you know, it's just the way it is
and, you know, there's just an abundance
of of bright, you know, like-minded
individuals who know football and, you
know, are able to communicate it. So,
um, it's a tough spot to fill and, uh, I
think we're just I'm super stoked for
Blau. He's a, you know, incredibly
talented and smart guy. So, I know he's
going to get us going on the right right
path.
>> We'll go back to K.
>> Thank you. Sorry about that. Hey,
Andrew. Um, you also have a new line
coach or Darnell Stapleton getting a
potion, Bobby leaving. What What can you
say about Darnell and that transition?
>> Um, I love Coach Tape, you know, you
know, and Shane. And so, you know,
having those guys, um, you know, have a,
you know, more integral role this
season. Uh, it's going to be great. You
know, you know, one of the best things
that Stape does, uh, is his game day
communication. Um, you know, he's a past
player. Uh, he's lived this life. you
know, he knows what it is to sit in that
bench with your guys beside you. And so,
you know, just how you know, he
reiterates certain points, you know, and
the little things he gives you here and
there, you know, especially on Sundays
is uh, you know, super important.
>> And and you and I know Nick, you kind of
brought this up, but you could have
tested. What What Why did you want to
get this done beforehand? And what makes
you want to come back to this group?
>> Um, this is a special group, you know,
not only players, um, but everyone in
this building. um in this place, you
know, we can win a lot of football games
here and, you know, I know it. Uh that's
why I signed back last year. Uh that's
why I signed back this year. You know, I
know we can win a lot of games here. The
culture is in place. You know, DQ and AP
have this place going. It's unlock. And
you know, we just got to, you know, step
up. You know, take it to that extra
step, make a little playoff run and and
get to the big one. And so, just like I
know we can
David.
>> Hey, Andrew. Congratulations. Uh,
welcome back. With with all the change
that's about to happen this season, some
people hate and resist change. Some
people love change and and roll with the
excitement that comes with it. And I
think most people are probably somewhere
in the middle. Where do you kind of fall
into that spectrum?
>> Um, I tend to, you know, I tend to run a
little little hot anyway. I tend to just
like stay excited like I'm here in the
building and dapping up everyone that
you know I haven't seen in a couple
months and uh just feeling great and so
um you know I'm welcoming all the new
changes um some new fresh blood some
ideas um you know I think it'll
definitely work in our favor
>> and then you and Nick Aligretti came
over from a championship caliber
organization obviously you arrived a
year before Nick did but to have that
running mate with you uh through these
last couple of seasons and to now be
able to move forward as teammates the
end. How how impactful is that for you?
>> Uh super. Um you know, it's not it's not
one of those things that happens in the
NFL today. You know, you get to, you
know, be on your team with with your
best friend, you know, for the longest,
you know, and it's rare to even have one
of those guys that you meet in the NFL.
So, uh super stoked for Nikki uh to get
in this building and sign and and uh and
you know, play the position that he
really is, you know, super confident in
as well. And so, you know, sky's is the
limit for Nikki. I'm just super stoked
we get to get another crack at this
thing.
>> Thanks, Andrew.
Andy,
>> hey, Andrew. Congratulations. Good to
see you. Um, so you just mentioned a
moment ago about the culture and I know
we often talk a lot about that piece of
it, what what AP and and and what DQ
have done for the culture here. Can you
just share a couple of examples of what
the what this culture is with the
Washington Commanders and why it was so
important for you to come back?
>> Well, you know, just looking back on
like, you know, different phases and
processes and levels of football, you
know, like no one's really trying to to
run you in the ground and break you and
and really see what kind of man you are
you like necessarily.
um we do that in different ways, you
know, you don't and so no one's really
trying to like break you down. It's all
about building you up here and just the
overwhelming positivity that that
creates uh really, you know, helps with
the energy in the building uh and the
positivity and just how people view
practice, lifts, certain drills at
practice and just just everything. And
so, um, it's definitely a positive
environment to be a part of.
>> And from the offensive line perspective,
you know, your first year with
Commanders, of course, it was an up
year, then last year down year. What did
what have you learned about yourself and
and your role in the offensive line and
and you all getting better as a unit?
>> Um, we've had some really tight groups
of of O lines here and just, you know,
some of the more skilled guys that I've
ever played around with. um you know in
in the pads it's some really talented
guys and so um but for me personally
it's you know I'm going to keep fighting
and uh I'm really trying to get on that
field any way I can and so u but
supporting my guys comes first being a
good teammate um you know and then you
know how the chips may fall is you know
I would just love to be out there uh
with the guys and so that's always my
goal but you know being a good teammate
and and someone that anyone could talk
to advice. I mean, this is I'm going
into my 10th season at this. You know, I
know a lot about the game and so
constantly dropping knowledge on anyone
who asks for it. Um, but, you know,
really something special about being
part of those five guys that are out
there uh protecting our guy.
>> Thank you. Congratulations again.
>> Thank you.
>> And we'll finish up with Ben.
>> Hey Andrew, congratulations. Um,
obviously the change in coordinator and
we've heard, you know, probably Jaden
will be more under center maybe less no
huddle. What does that mean for an
offensive lineman? What's your sense of
what it changes to the offensive line
going from what you guys are running to
what we think it's going to be now?
>> Um well, you know, specifically with,
you know, no huddle offenses and things
close to that nature, you kind of just
uh the offensive line really only gets
their blocking responsibilities. They
don't necessarily get the strength of
the formation. um you know um things
like that, you know, where the running
back's lined up at. Um little things
that could help us on angles and
blocking points. Um but you know, when
you huddle up, you get the whole play
call, you kind of know where everyone's
lined up. The center can just, you know,
line up, get a point, you know, get the
hand on the rock and and let's roll. Um
so it's doesn't necessarily slow things
down uh too much, but it definitely
gives us upfront uh more information to
work with.
And obviously, um, Tyler Bottes is is,
uh, been released, not going to be with
you guys. I know it's not your call, but
what I guess what can you say about
being with Tyra the last couple years,
what do you kind of think is some of the
keys to whoever is going to replace him?
>> Um, he he's a guy you want to have in
your locker room. He's a guy you want to
have on your team. And, um, you know, I
wish nothing but the best for Tai. I
think it caught some of us um, in shock,
but that's just kind of the nature of
the business. Um, but he is a great
person, uh, and a great football player
and so I know he's going to be all right
for himself. He's gonna do all right.
Um, but just a, you know, just a great
guy. Someone you want in the locker room
for sure.
>> All right. Thanks, Andrew.
>> Appreciate it, guys. Thank you.
>> Stand by. We're going to studio next.
Yep.
Walk down second.